[{"answer": "Stolen", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " You left the door open?", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, I got caught up... watching a soap opera... The Bold and the Beautifu", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Wide open", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How do you get all that wood in here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "They deliver wood", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " I didn't know there was a fireplace", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "A garden! I can't believe there's a garden", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You can", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You can tip a gardener", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Thank you very much", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You could take it? You want it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You could take it? You want it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "So you do want it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No, I don't want it. I want it, if you don't want it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No I, I want it if you don't want it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You just said, you wanted it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " So take it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying, if a situation arose in which you didn't want it, I might take it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " How can I take it?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " So take it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How can I take it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "All right, now you call it in the air", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No no", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "INTERFERENCE! YOU CAN'T COUNT THAT. COME ON, ARE YOU CRAZY?!! THE COIN CAN NOT TOUCH ANYTHING, it affects it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "YOU DON'T HAVE TO CALL THAT. THAT'S A RULE!", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, me neither", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Definitely", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Definitely", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No, it's not a problem, I can get rid of the apartment this afternoon.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "If only the coin hadn't hit the table", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "It is not", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "The table is interference, you know it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It is too", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "We're aware of the proximity to the park, yes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Robbery.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Nice meeting you.", "qsentId": 38}]